When the stakes are this high, they’ll get one chance of...
Going for Gold is a drama, family film directed by Clay Glen.
Seventeen year old, Emma joins a high school cheerleading team when she moves
to Australia with her dad who is a former Air Force Officer.
Emma, played by Kelli Berglund.
Hannah, played by Emily Morris.
Susan, played by Jo Stone.
Coach Caitlyn, played by Ruth Fallon.
Mia, played by Jess Kuss.
Abi, played by Elysia Markou.
Gold: The Dream That United Our Nation, or simply Gold, is a 2018 Indian Hindi-language period sports
film written and directed by Reema Kagti and produced by Farhan Akhtar and Ritesh Sidhwani.
The film stars an ensemble cast of Akshay Kumar, Mouni Roy, Amit Sadh, Kunal
Kapoor, Vineet Kumar Singh, Sunny Kaushal and Nikita Dutta.
Gold is based on the journey of India's national hockey team to the 1948 Summer Olympics and
follows Tapan Das, the man who won India its first gold medal in the same event.
Gold was theatrically released on 15 August 2018
during India's Independence Day.
The film grossed ₹158 crore (US$19 million) against a budget of ₹61 crore (US$7.2 million) at the
box office Gold also became the first Bollywood film to be released in Saudi Arabia.
The tone is emotional.